[
 {
   "No": 1,
   "Quiz question": "Who is the fourth musketeer besides D Artagnan, Athos and Porthos?",
   "Answer": "Aramis"
 },
 {
   "No": 2,
   "Quiz question": "Who killed the Minotaur ?",
   "Answer": "Theseus"
 },
 {
   "No": 3,
   "Quiz question": "Which Egyptian woman was considered as the inventor of agriculture? She married her brother and together they had a son: Horus.",
   "Answer": "Isis"
 },
 {
   "No": 4,
   "Quiz question": "Who is the giant with 100 eyes according to the Greek mythology?",
   "Answer": "Argus"
 },
 {
   "No": 5,
   "Quiz question": "Whose box did Epimethius open?",
   "Answer": "Pandora s box"
 },
 {
   "No": 6,
   "Quiz question": "What is the name of the winged horse in Greek mythology?",
   "Answer": "Pegasus"
 },
 {
   "No": 7,
   "Quiz question": "Who wrote Oliver Twist?",
   "Answer": "Charles Dickens"
 },
 {
   "No": 8,
   "Quiz question": "On which island did Ernest Hemingway stay to be able to write much?",
   "Answer": "Cuba"
 },
 {
   "No": 9,
   "Quiz question": "Where is set the book A Small Town in Germany by John Le Carre?",
   "Answer": "Bonn"
 },
 {
   "No": 10,
   "Quiz question": "In which country did Shakespeare s Hamlet live?",
   "Answer": "Denmark"
 },
 {
   "No": 11,
   "Quiz question": "Who was the wife of Othello?",
   "Answer": "Desdemona"
 },
 {
   "No": 12,
   "Quiz question": "Who was the imaginary love of Don Quixote?",
   "Answer": "Dulcinea"
 },
 {
   "No": 13,
   "Quiz question": "In which two languages did the Irish writer Samuel Beckett write?",
   "Answer": "English and French"
 },
 {
   "No": 14,
   "Quiz question": "Which book Mary Shelley wrote when she was 19?",
   "Answer": "Frankenstein"
 },
 {
   "No": 15,
   "Quiz question": "Who said \"I think therefore I am\"?",
   "Answer": "Rene Descartes"
 },
 {
   "No": 16,
   "Quiz question": "What is the English name of the Russian novel titled Voyna i Mir?",
   "Answer": "War and peace"
 },
 {
   "No": 17,
   "Quiz question": "What is the name of the infamous novel by Vladimir Nabokov?",
   "Answer": "Lolita"
 },
 {
   "No": 18,
   "Quiz question": "In which book did Sherlock Holmes first show up?",
   "Answer": "Study In Scarlet"
 },
 {
   "No": 19,
   "Quiz question": "What is the name of the first complete novel written by Charles Dickens?",
   "Answer": "The Pickwick Papers"
 },
 {
   "No": 20,
   "Quiz question": "In which part of Shakespeare do you find the character Ophelia?",
   "Answer": "Hamlet"
 },
 {
   "No": 21,
   "Quiz question": "Who is the hero in the book Da Vinci Code?",
   "Answer": "Professor Robert Langdon"
 },
 {
   "No": 22,
   "Quiz question": "Who wrote Moby Dick?",
   "Answer": "Herman Melville"
 },
 {
   "No": 23,
   "Quiz question": "Who solves the crime in \"Death on the Nile\"?",
   "Answer": "Hercule Poirot"
 },
 {
   "No": 24,
   "Quiz question": "Who wrote Jungle Book?",
   "Answer": "Rudyard Kipling"
 }
]